expatwomen.com 2009-06-19

# Expat Women - Helping Expatriate Women Living Overseas - Expat Relocation Abroad - Expat Blogs

This site is owned and operated by Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd. We give full respect to your privacy and confidential contact information. This statement explains our policies and practices regarding the use and disclosure of your personal information by Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd. Please note that, Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd reviews and updates this Privacy Policy from time to time as needed without notice. Therefore, you should review the terms of this policy periodically to make sure that you are aware of how Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd collects and uses personal information. By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd as explained below.    

1\. Personal Information

You may visit www.expatwomen.com anonymously as often as you like without providing any personally identifying information (such as your name, address or e-mail address). Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd does not collect personally identifying information from you except when you specifically provide it, and Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd endeavours to protect the information it receives. You will come across places where Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd will ask you to voluntarily provide us with information about yourself (for example, when you sign up for our newsletter, submit a story, make a comment on a story, submit a bloglink, submit a city experience, or other such requests). All of these activities are purely voluntary; if you do not wish to reveal your personal information, you are free simply to ignore these sections of our site. If you decide to participate, we will not use your personal information for any purpose other than expressed below and you hereby grant us your authorization to us to proceed accordingly.

If Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd asks for your personal information on bulletin boards or comment submission (or similar sections of the site), it is simply so that other people reading a string of comments will be able to determine which comments come from the same person. You may, therefore, provide a nickname or alias, if you prefer, so that your identity is not disclosed. You should be aware that if you do voluntarily disclose personal information (e.g. user name, e-mail address) on the bulletin boards, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or parties. If you choose to participate anonymously, you should remember that you are still legally liable for the material you post, including claims of libel, invasion of privacy and copyright infringement.

Some of the main areas Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd asks for your personal information include when you submit a story, city experience or a bloglink. Once you have submitted your information via our online submission form or via email, you have agreed to let us reveal some personal information on our web site (including first name, nationality, current country, countries lived in, biography, languages spoken and a photo. Any other personal information provided may be used by Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd to communicate with you regarding winning a prize (your email address, mailing address information) etc. 

2\. Use of Personal information

We will use your personal information solely for purpose of designing a web site that’s content is suitable to your needs. 

Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd does track user traffic patterns throughout our site. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. We do break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser). We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and do not like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

3\. Disclosure of Personal information

Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd will not knowingly give away, rent, or sell any information to third parties regarding your name, e-mail address, or other information you send us through inquiries, submissions, or subscriptions.

4\. Accuracy and Security

The accuracy and security of the personal information is important to Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd. Currently, you may request updates to your personal information retained by Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd. If you [Contact Us](mailto:contactus@expatwomen.com?subject=ExpatWomen%20Updates:%20Genuine%20Contact) to correct your personal information, we will attempt to correct such inaccuracies in a timely manner. If you have previously provided us with your [Contact Us](mailto:contactus@expatwomen.com?subject=ExpatWomen:%20Genuine%20Contact). We will try to accommodate your request, but cannot promise that it will happen immediately. Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd is concerned with the security of your Personal information and is committed to taking reasonable steps to protect it from unauthorized access and use of that personal information. __

5\. External Links

Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd web site provides links to other third party web sites. Even if the third party is affiliated with Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd through a business partnership or otherwise, Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices or the content of such external links. These links are provided to you for convenience purposes only and you access them at your own risk. 

8\. Terms of Use

Please also see our Terms and Conditions, which describes the restrictions, disclaimers, indemnification and limitation of liability governing the use of the entire Expat Women Enterprises Pty Ltd web site. 

9\. General

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, please [Contact Us](mailto:contactus@expatwomen.com?subject=ExpatWomen:%20Genuine%20Contact%20-%20Privacy%20Policy).
